homebusinesscenter.com 2013-03-16

# HBC Inc Privacy Policy, Copyright Notice and Liability Disclaimer

> * * *
> 
> _HomeBusinessCenter.com does not give, sell, rent, share or trade any identifiable personal information to any third party regarding our website visitors or newsletter subscribers._
> 
> We are committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our website. You can access HomeBusinessCenter.com and browse our website without disclosing any of your personal data. HomeBusinessCenter.com does not collect personal information about individuals, such as names or email addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual, and he or she has agreed to the terms under which HomeBusinessCenter.com will use it.
> 
> HomeBusinessCenter.com will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.
> 
> Materials appearing on HomeBusinessCenter.com are copyright. Permission to reprint or electronically reproduce any document or graphic is expressly prohibited unless prior written consent is obtained from HomeBusinessCenter.com.
> 
> HomeBusinessCenter.com is designed to help visitors obtain information and guidance in the area of home business. This information service is continually under development. While we try to keep the information up-to-date and accurate, we can make no guarantees as to the performance of each individual company.
> 
> We believe that the information dispensed is accurate and reliable, but in some instances the information may represent opinion or judgement. Responses from HomeBusinessCenter.com to questions relating to the home business industry should in no way be regarded as a complete analysis of the subject matter.
> 
> HomeBusinessCenter.com provides links to other remote websites. Therefore, we are not responsible for the content or guarantees of the products and services they provide.
> 
> HomeBusinessCenter.com cannot guarantee any amount of income from a business opportunity or profits from a marketing service since each individual and every home business is different. Your participation in these business opportunities and services is solely at your own risk.
> 
> Third Party Ads: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
> 
> This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service which uses cookies', which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site.
> 
> If you have any questions, please do not hesitate to contact us directly at **HomeBusinessCenter.com**
> 
> **Affiliate Disclosure & Sponsorship Ads:**
> 
> Home Business Center, Inc. supports itself through third-party sponsorship ads and affiliate program partnerships. This means that when you click on links to websites mentioned on our website, they may or may not result in a commission that is credited to this site.
> 
> On this site, we write about and include only business ideas and marketing information that we think is useful and worthwhile, whether it be commissionable or not. Home Business Center, Inc. does not sell any products directly.
> 
> The products and services shown as third party ads (i.e Google Adsense) in the right-hand column of our web pages are not affiliated with Home Business Center, Inc..
> 
> Please contact us if you have any questions. We'd be happy to talk with you.
> 
> Thanks for visiting us!
